<Feed>Crime Junkie</Feed>
<items>
    <item>
        <title>ALL GOOD PEOPLE HERE…IS HERE!!</title>
        <date>Tue, 16 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</date>
        <link>https://www.ashleyflowers.com/book</link>
        <description>The day has FINALLY arrived, Crime Junkies!! Ashley Flowers\' debut novel ALL GOOD PEOPLE HERE is officially available NOW!If you haven’t already, go get your hands on a copy! You can find ALL GOOD PEOPLE HERE wherever books, ebooks, or audiobooks are sold or at AshleyFlowers.com/bookBe sure to follow us on Instagram at @crimejunkiepodcast to get in on all of the fun book conversations... AND if you love the book as much as we think you will, leave a review so we can see all of your thoughts & theories.Happy reading, Crime Junkies!For more information about all things Ashley and All Good People Here, visit AshleyFlowers.comNorth America Crime Junkies can order here:https://www.penguinrandomhouse.com/books/691141/all-good-people-here-by-ashley-flowers/UK + Commonwealth Crime Junkies can order here:https://www.amazon.co.uk/All-Good-People-Here-gripping/dp/0008503109/ref=tmm_hrd_swat[%E2%80%A6]encoding=UTF8&qid=1641811155&sr=1-1&tag=linkfire-smarturl-21 </description>
    </item>
    <item>
        <title>MURDERED: Shari Smith and Debra Helmick</title>
        <date>Mon, 15 Aug 2022 07:00:00 +0000</date>
        <link>https://crimejunkiepodcast.com/</link>
        <description>When 17-year-old Shari Smith is abducted from her driveway in broad daylight, it seems like her family’s nightmare can’t get any worse. But when her abductor starts calling them relentlessly, investigators hope that his recklessness will lead to his downfall... that is, until a second girl goes missing in an eerily similar manner.John Douglas\' bookWhen a Killer CallsFor current Fan Club membership options and policies, please visit https://crimejunkieapp.com/library/.Source materials for this episode cannot be listed here due to character limitations. For a full list of sources, please visit: https://crimejunkiepodcast.com/murdered-shari-smith-debra-helmick/ </description>
    </item>
</items>